### r00t4bl3.com

### Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

By [r00t4bl3](https://r00t4bl3.com/)

Jul 1, 2019

> This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website.

Welcome to r00t4bl3
-------------------

#### Your privacy is critically important to us..

It is r00t4bl3's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [https://r00t4bl3.com](https://r00t4bl3.com/) (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "r00t4bl3"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, r00t4bl3 collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. r00t4bl3's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how r00t4bl3's visitors use its website. From time to time, r00t4bl3 may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

r00t4bl3 also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://r00t4bl3.com blog posts. r00t4bl3 only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to r00t4bl3's websites choose to interact with r00t4bl3 in ways that require r00t4bl3 to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that r00t4bl3 gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://r00t4bl3.com to provide a username and email address.

#### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Advertisements

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by r00t4bl3 and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### Google AdWords

Google use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy.

#### Links To External Sites

Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

#### Aggregated Statistics

r00t4bl3 may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. r00t4bl3 may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, r00t4bl3 does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

To enrich and perfect your online experience, r00t4bl3 uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. r00t4bl3 uses cookies to help r00t4bl3 identify and track visitors, their usage of https://r00t4bl3.com, and their website access preferences. r00t4bl3 visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using r00t4bl3's websites, with the drawback that certain features of r00t4bl3's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to r00t4bl3's use of cookies.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, r00t4bl3 may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in r00t4bl3's sole discretion. r00t4bl3 encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

#### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms of Use.

### Popular Posts

    #### [How to Install MySQL/MariaDB Server on Raspberry Pi](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-install-mysql-mariadb-server-on-raspberry-pi)
    
    Jul 5, 2018

    #### [How to Install PostgreSQL 11 on Linux Mint 19 Tara](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-install-postgresql-11-on-linux-mint-19-tara)
    
    Oct 26, 2018

    #### [How to Fix Error ASCII while Restoring Database from MySQL Dump](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-fix-error-ascii-while-restoring-database-from-mysql-dump)
    
    Feb 22, 2021

    #### [How to Hide nginx Web Server Version Signature and Remove X-Powered-By PHP Header on CentOS](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-hide-nginx-web-server-version-signature-and-remove-x-powered-by-php-header-on-centos)
    
    Jul 17, 2018

    #### [How to Install Postman Native App in Linux Mint 18.3 Sylvia](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-install-postman-native-app-in-linux-mint-18-3-sylvia)
    
    Feb 6, 2018

### Latest Posts

    Oct 15, 2024
    
    #### [How to Install PostgreSQL 17 on Ubuntu 24.04 LTS Noble Numbat](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-install-postgresql-17-on-ubuntu-24-04-lts-noble-numbat)

    Aug 21, 2023
    
    #### [How to Install XFCE desktop in Fedora 38](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-install-xfce-desktop-in-fedora-38)

    Oct 21, 2022
    
    #### [Laravel API Resources: How to remove meta and links property from ResourceCollection](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/laravel-api-resources-how-to-remove-meta-and-links-property-from-resourcecollection)

    Aug 10, 2022
    
    #### [How to Install FreeBSD 13.1](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-install-freebsd-13-1)

    Aug 3, 2022
    
    #### [How to Install Ubuntu Server 22.04 Jammy Jellyfish LTS](https://r00t4bl3.com/post/how-to-install-ubuntu-server-22-04-jammy-jellyfish-lts)

© Copyright 2024 [r00t4bl3.com](https://r00t4bl3.com/). All rights reserved.
